{
    "id": "69102c9357e44069b5c64cc87e1b64c3",
    "title": "Though, Even Though, If, Even If",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "951924ebe3464c97a76e797e4f7b884a",
            "title": "Though, If, Even Though, Even If",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "………………………. I was not feeling well, I enjoyed the party.",
                    "description": "Even though is a more emphatic version of though. It is possible in situations where though is also correct. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Even though",
                        "Even if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. she apologizes, we cannot take her back.",
                    "description": "Even if refers to the present or future. Even though has a past reference. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Even if",
                        "Even though",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………… you are busy, I will wait outside.",
                    "description": "If expresses a condition. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Even if",
                        "If",
                        "Though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. he is quite busy, he always finds time for his family.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "Even though",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. that is your decision, there is nothing that I can do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Even if",
                        "Even though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. we suffered a crushing defeat, we didn’t lose hope.",
                    "description": "Even though is a more emphatic form of though. They are both possible here. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Even though",
                        "Even if",
                        "Though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………………….. she was ill, she refused to take the medication.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "If",
                        "Even if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………… it was an expensive laptop, I bought it.",
                    "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "If",
                        "Even if"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. you forbid me, I will go.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Even if",
                        "Even though",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………………. they tried hard, they could not save him.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Though",
                        "If",
                        "Even though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………. you work hard now, it is not possible to catch up with them.",
                    "description": "Even if used to talk about situations that are true in the present or future. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "If",
                        "Even if",
                        "Even though"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………… I had studied well, I could not get good marks.",
                    "description": "Even though is an emphatic form of though. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "Even though",
                        "Even if",
                        "If"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}